http://www.nuwireinvestor.com/privacy-policy/

HomePrivacy Policy
We at NuWire, Inc. appreciate you visiting NuWireInvestor.com. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on this website.
THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT
On NuWireInvestor.com, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online magazine or participate in one of our online forums. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services.
There are certain circumstances where you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person’s name and e-mail address to send an article, a sponsored subscription or a promotional offer. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient’s name, address, e-mail address and telephone number.
We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows Vista, Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Verizon, AOL).
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.
We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our registration agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online magazine or to contact you about your account with us.
We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts or free promotional items. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs or services to them.
The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs or services.
If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a “letter to our editors”), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs or services.
We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.
Agents and contractors of NuWire who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for NuWire.
Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.
NuWire will not disclose personally identifiable information to other companies (other than NuWire or any of its subsidiaries), unless: You request to have your personal information disclosed in order to receive additional information, promotional offers and/or follow up; and/or It is disclosed as part of an opt-in promotional offer that some of your personal information will be disclosed to another company.
We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, you can opt out using the unsubscribe button at the bottom of any promotional e-mails. NuWire will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.
COOKIES
To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.
We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize your name when you return to the website or identify articles of interest), save your password in password-protected areas and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services.
COLLECTION OF INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTY SITES, AD SERVERS AND SPONSORS
NuWire may from time to time include links to other websites. These websites may have different information practices. Visitors should consult the other websites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.
NuWire may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. NuWire has no control over these third parties’ use of this information. The NuWire website will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.
NuWire may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy.
OUR COMMITMENT TO SECURITY
We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online.
HOW YOU CAN ACCESS OR CORRECT INFORMATION
If any of your personally identifiable information is incorrect, please contact us at customerservice@nuwireinvestor.com.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions or concerns about NuWire’s online privacy policy for this site or its implementation, you may contact us at customerservice@nuwireinvestor.com.
UPDATES & EFFECTIVE DATE
From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we disclose it.
Share This:
StocksToTrade 2020 Review: A One-Stop-Shop Trading Powerhouse for Traders
Abu Dhabi Real Estate Holistic Property Management
FDH Bank Launches FDH WhatsApp Banking
Bitcoin Profit – Is It A Safe Platform?
Bitcoin Revolution – Can I Rely On This Platform?
Recent Updates
How To Start A Business In Your RV
Assessing Your Risk When Investing in an Existing Business
It’s the Pandemic Not Me – How to Deal with Overdue Invoices from Clients
GuidesSelf-Directed IRA Information
Life Insurance as an Investment
Mortgage Rate Information
Find Businesses For Sale
© 2018 NuWireInvestor.com .
Back to top
Loading...
Loading...
